companydata.in 2016-12-02

# Privacy policy - Company Data

We pay much attention to the privacy policy and personal data of our users. Here we will briefly describe what kind of data we use, what aim we follow and the terms on which we provide information for public access. Any information received from our customers (name, e-mail etc.) remain closed to all and will never be available to third persons. Therefore, any our visitor who has applied to us can be sure about absolute anonymity. In case of any questions related to our site and information posted on it - contact us without hesitation.

## **What data we collect**

All data we collect includes the following information: contact information (including email address, and phone number), name, title and company name. We also have information about the country and the city from which the entry was done to our information resource.

## **How do we use your data**

All data we use for internal needs of our organization aimed at improving the quality of our services and products. We do not use these data for spamming and will not share this information with third persons for the implementation of such actions. We do not also sell or lease the data received from you. Our aim is providing exclusively all our customers maximum comfort and convenience on our website.

## **Other provisions of the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the full right to modify, add or delete certain parts of this privacy policy at any time, also while visiting our site, you agree to all the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or problems, please contact us by clicking on Contact us button.
